webpackJsonp([65856866535745],{157:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function r(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e:{default:e}}function l(e,a){if(!(e instanceof a))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}function o(e,a){if(!e)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return!a||"object"!=typeof a&&"function"!=typeof a?e:a}function i(e,a){if("function"!=typeof a&&null!==a)throw new TypeError("Super expression must either be null or a function, not "+typeof a);e.prototype=Object.create(a&&a.prototype,{constructor:{value:e,enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0}}),a&&(Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e,a):e.__proto__=a)}a.__esModule=!0;var n=t(1),c=r(n),s=t(102),d=r(s),u=t(158),m=r(u),f=t(38),p=(r(f),t(39)),h=(r(p),t(40)),b=(r(h),function(e){function a(){return l(this,a),o(this,e.apply(this,arguments))}return i(a,e),a.prototype.render=function(){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container py-5"},c.default.createElement("section",{className:"professional_builder row "},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.default.createElement("section",{className:"about_us_area row py-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"row about_row"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"who_we_area col-md-6 col-sm-6 mb-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"subtittle "},c.default.createElement("h2",{className:"display-4 text-uppercase font-400"},"let′s get in touch"),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"divider-black-left"})),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"single-contact-info d-flex h-auto"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"contact-icon mr-15 "},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"address icon-box mb-4"},c.default.createElement("h2",{className:"featurette-heading py-2 pl-2"},c.default.createElement("i",{className:"address fas fa-map-marker-alt"})))),c.default.createElement("h5",{className:"text-left black ml-4 pt-3"},"3201 Antel Global Corporate Center, J. Vargas Ave., Ortigas Center, Pasig City")),c.default.createElement(m.default,{height:"40vh"})),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6 col-sm-6 about_client about-left"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"page-title text-center mb-4"},c.default.createElement("h4",{className:"title display-5"},"Contact Us"),c.default.createElement("p",{className:"pt-3"},"Interested in working together? We′re approachable and would love to speak to you. Feel free to call, send us an email or simply complete the enquiry form.")),c.default.createElement(d.default,null))))))))},a}(n.Component));a.default=b,e.exports=a.default},478:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function r(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e:{default:e}}function l(e,a){if(!(e instanceof a))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}function o(e,a){if(!e)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return!a||"object"!=typeof a&&"function"!=typeof a?e:a}function i(e,a){if("function"!=typeof a&&null!==a)throw new TypeError("Super expression must either be null or a function, not "+typeof a);e.prototype=Object.create(a&&a.prototype,{constructor:{value:e,enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0}}),a&&(Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e,a):e.__proto__=a)}a.__esModule=!0;var n=t(1),c=r(n),s=t(19),d=r(s),u=t(157),m=(r(u),t(46)),f=r(m),p=t(54),h=r(p),b=[{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"1Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-1",href:"#collapse-1",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"2Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-2",href:"#collapse-2",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"3Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-3",href:"#collapse-3",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"4Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-4",href:"#collapse-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"5Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-5",href:"#collapse-5",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"6Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-6",href:"#collapse-6",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"7Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-7",href:"#collapse-7",display:!0}],y=[{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"1Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-1",href:"#collapse-tab2-1",display:!0},{question:"Who owns Wikipedia?",answer:"2Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-2",href:"#collapse-tab2-2",display:!0},{question:"Why am I having trouble logging in?",answer:"3Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-3",href:"#collapse-tab2-3",display:!0},{question:"How can I contact Wikipedia?",answer:"4Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-4",href:"#collapse-tab2-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"5Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-5",href:"#collapse-tab2-5",display:!0},{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"6Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-6",href:"#collapse-tab2-6",display:!0}],w=(b.reverse(),y.reverse(),function(e){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"card"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"card-header panel-heading",role:"tab",id:"headingOne"},c.default.createElement("a",{role:"button",className:"collapsed text-black","data-toggle":"collapse","data-parent":"#accordion","data-core":"",href:e.href,"aria-expanded":"false","aria-controls":"collapse1"},c.default.createElement("p",{className:"lead black display-5 mr-3"},c.default.createElement("span",{className:"sign mbr-iconfont mbri-arrow-down inactive"})," ",e.question))),c.default.createElement("div",{id:e.id,className:"panel-collapse noScroll collapse",role:"tabpanel","aria-labelledby":"headingOne"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"panel-body p-4"},c.default.createElement("p",{className:"mbr-fonts-style panel-text display-7"},e.answer))))}),E=b.map(w),g=E.slice(0,5),N=y.map(w),v=N.slice(0,5),q=function(e){function a(){return l(this,a),o(this,e.apply(this,arguments))}return i(a,e),a.prototype.render=function(){return c.default.createElement("div",{className:"pt-5",id:"content-14"},c.default.createElement(f.default,{title:"Frequently Asked Questions",breadcrumbItem1:"home /",href1:"./",breadcrumbItem2:"faQ ",active2:"active"}),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container pt-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_rht ml-3 mr-3 mb-5 text-center"},c.default.createElement("h2",{className:"display-4 font-400"},"Have a Question?"),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.default.createElement("p",{className:"pt-2 pb-3 text-center"},"Here are the most frequently asked questions at Tatong. If you have a question not answered here - or throughout our website - please"," ",c.default.createElement(d.default,{className:"",to:"./contact"},"Contact Us"),"."))),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"row pt-4 pb-5"},c.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-6 col-md-10 col-sm-12 mx-auto mb-3"},c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2"},"Product"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),g),c.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-6 col-md-10 col-sm-12 mx-auto"},c.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2"},"Sales"),c.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),v))),c.default.createElement(h.default,null))},a}(n.Component);a.default=q,e.exports=a.default}});
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-fa-q-js-2d45a945dbae73cf02d4.js.map